A Guide to the Marcia A. T. Thompson papers FA1489
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arts Stabilization Projects, 1936-2000; 3; 12.99 Cubic Feet 28 letter document boxes and 5 legal document boxes
  - School of American Ballet - Ford Foundation National Program, 1963-1974 (Box 33, Folder 341)
  - Ford Foundation Ballet Conference, 1961 June-August (Box 33, Folder 342)
  - Reviews of Visits to Ballet Schools, 1960-1963 (Box 33, Folder 343)
    1. Visits to St. Louis, Cincinnati, and Dayton
    2. Leningrad, The Kirov Choreographic Academy
  - School of American Ballet - Annual Reports to the Ford Foundation, Supplement to 9 Years Reports, 1964-1972 (Box 33, Folder 344)
  - School of American Ballet - Correspondence (2 folders), 1959-2004 (Box 33, Folder 345-346)
    Includes correspondence with John D. Rockefeller 3rd regarding Lincoln Center
  - School of American Ballet - Report to the Ford Foundation, Evaluation of National Program, 1964-1973 (Box 33, Folder 347)
  - Responses to School of American Ballet - Questionnaires Concerning: Beginners' Groups Guest Teachers from SAB Students Awarded Local Scholarships (2 folders), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 348-349)
    Folder 348:
    Alabama
    Arizona
    California
    Connecticut
    Delaware
    Florida
    Georgia
    Haiti
    Illinois
    Louisiana
    Maryland
    Massachusetts
    Michigan
    Missouri
    Nebraska
    New Jersey
    Folder 349:
    New Mexico
    New York
    North Carolina
    Ohio
    Oklahoma
    Pennsylvania
    Puerto Rico
    South Carolina
    Tennessee
    Texas
    Utah
    Virginia
    Washington
    Washington, D.C.
    Wisconsin